worldbuzznow.com 2011-11-09

# Privacy Policy | World Buzz Now!

**Statement Regarding Privacy Policy**

WorldBuzzNow! recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our customers. For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, the word customers includes visitors to our web sites, subscribers to and users of our services and advertising customers.

**Personal Information**

WBN! collects personal information when we provide some of our services to you. Generally we will tell you why we are collecting information when we collect it and how we plan to use it. In some instances, collection of personal information will be obvious and WBN! will not anymore publish a statement.

We usually collect personal information such as your name and email address for subscriptions. As a general rule we do not collect sensitive information. However, if we do, it will usually be for the purposes of providing our services and if the law requires us to, we will seek your consent to collect it.

**Use of Information**

We use your information to provide our services to you, to fulfill administrative functions associated with these services.

We may share your information with other companies which are related to WBN!. We or they may also use your personally identifiable information to assist us in improving our services.

We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our services including our Web pages for your computer (e.g., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content here at WBN!.

**Security**

WorldBuzzNow! strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information of our users. We use a variety of physical and electronic security measures including firewalls and secure databases on our web hosting provider to keep personal information secure from misuse, loss or unauthorized use or disclosure.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure.

**Access to Personal Information**

You have a right to access most personal information we hold about you and if we deny access in some circumstances we will tell you why.

To request access, please contact our privacy officer as set out at the end of this document.

**Public Information**

Any information posted on the comments section and/or communicated in chat areas becomes public information.

**Cookies**

_Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes._

Cookies can facilitate a user’s ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature.

**Online Links to Third Party Websites**

WorldBuzzNow! may establish relationships with other websites. These sites may collect personal information from you that may be shared with us. This Privacy Statement will apply to any personal information we obtain in this manner.

WorldBuzzNow! is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our sites. These links are meant for the user’s convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by WorldBuzzNow! of the content, policies or practices of those third party sites. Once you have left our site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.

If you have any queries regarding the access to your information or if you have a complaint, please contact person below.

Niño Yeh  
ninyeh [@] gmail.com
